Good, good, good, look deep into the eyes
Make it a fleeting memory This is already a cover, isn't it?
Hello everyone. I'm Miku Kanemura from Minatozaka 46.
Today, I've been entrusted with a very important task.
I'd like to have the star of the show.
Hello. I'm Takahashi Mikuji of Minato Zaka 46.
What's with the furisode?
This time, we're going to have Miku Kanamura, who loves cameras, take a before picture for us.
Thank you very much.
You were saying that, weren't you? Yes, I was.
I was pretty much halfway up the stairs when I said I'd like to have Miku take some prenotification shots.
It really turned out to be a project.
She said she wanted to do it, so we made it happen.
Congratulations on your wedding!
This time, I'm what you might call a mama-furi. I'm here.
I wore my mother's furisode (long-sleeved kimono), and I put a lot of thought into my hair.
She wore her hair blonde and everything. It's so cute.
It's so cute. It makes a great picture.
Please take nice pictures of me. I'll take lots of pictures today.
I'll have fun. I'll take stylish shots.
It looks really good on you. Great.
That's what I'm talking about. Cheese, Stan.
Stan, check. Check.
Check it out.
I just got a new lens, and it's got these flares in it.
I'm using one right now, and the flares are all around the top, like a bunch of lights or something. I'm using it right now, and the flares are all over the top, and sometimes there's just a lot of light.
Here we go. - Cheese, cheese, cheese, cheese, cheese, cheese, cheese, cheese, cheese.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes. Cute.
Nervous, nervous, nervous. Why?
Wait a minute.
The light is amazing! That kind of lens will have a rainbow in it this time.
I want to put a rainbow in it. That's what I want to do.
A little bit of flare. Oh, my God.
It's the rainbow of the three countries.
So stylish!
It's been like this the whole time, so my voice...
It's good. - Yes, yes, yes.
Nice, pretty. You're a good photographer.
Nice subject, good photographer.
It's nice. It's nice. I'm happy.
I have to focus on this one myself.
Look at the eyes. Look deep into the eyes.
Important, important, important.
I'm sure your fans will see it, and your family too.
You want to keep it, don't you?
It's nice. It looks good. Okay, okay, okay.
It's like this. It's nice. It's nice.
It's fun having the members as photographers.
They put up a lot of pictures of how cute they are. It'll be a memory for a lifetime.
I've never done this before.
I've had them model for me a little bit, but... I've been doing things with models for a while now and then.
But this is the first time I've done it with someone watching.
I'm sorry. I get so nervous. I get so nervous.
From the top. -She's cute.
She's beautiful. Her face is nice. Nice.
Beautiful. So cute.
Like this.
She's a big sister.
She's beautiful, but really...
Yes, yes, yes.
It's fun. I'm already looking forward to the finished product.
Here's a big one.
I always bring these to job sites.
This one is a little closer to the face.
It's a little beautiful.
Even closer.
Cute!
Damn!
Wait, is he eating something?
Oh, he's so cute.
It's attacking me every time I take a picture.
No, it's good. It's good.
It's good, it's good. It's beautiful. It's beautiful.
It's like this.
Oh, nice. Oh, okay.
That's a clap.
Thank you very much. It's a clap.
It's great. It's great. It's great.
Let's take another shot of the fluffy version.
I like it.
Ha, ha!
Watch out.
The diamonds.
There'll be diamonds for the rest of our lives.
Sudden pressure
This is good.
Nice?
I don't know what's going on here.
I don't know what it is, but...
Flare?
I like the flare.
Flare.
That's good.
No, thank you.
We're taking a break. We are taking a break.
One hour has passed.
We had a lot of pictures taken.
I'm sorry for being so low.
We were both having fun.
Please introduce your camera. Please introduce me to your camera.
The main one is this Sony Alpha 7 III.
Cannon. Such a long one.
This is the first lens I bought.
This can be used for everything. Versatile.
It's a little bit heavy.
It can be used for wide-angle landscapes or
In the kitchen garden, it's great for portraits.
It can take pictures of people.
I think it's pretty good.
I also brought my
I brought a film camera that I always use, a Contax
Carl's Ice, a famous lens manufacturer
I can use a lens from a famous lens manufacturer
which is a famous lens manufacturer called Carl's Ice.
The bokeh effect of this lens is great.
I recommend it.
It's cute. Also, the form looks like a camera.
It looks like a camera, and the camera looks like a camera, so it's really fun to hold.
I am currently studying at Nihon University's College of Art.
Actually, I'm in my third year.
I'm in my third year, and I'm studying photography,
I hope to be able to take pictures for this kind of work someday.
My dream is to make a photo book of the members.
That is another dream of mine.
Please, anyone, please consider it. Anyone please consider this.
I need to brush up on my skills.
Are there a lot of practical skills?
Yes, a lot of practical skills. I'm studying photography, so I have to draw pictures by hand.
We also do digital photography, but recently we have been doing things like rolling and burning silver film by ourselves.
In the current class, we mainly use silver film.
The kids are all really good at photography, so everyone around me is very impressed.
I'm learning a lot from them, so I may talk about that in the future.
If there is anything that you can entrust us with, like today, we would love to hear from you.
Thank you very much.
No, thank you very much.
Yay!
Hanging out in the city
Strolling the streets! I'm just looking for a nice little street corner.
I'm looking for a nice place
I'm looking for rainbows right now.
Oh, yeah, I'm looking for rainbows.
There's a railroad crossing over there.
Or a railroad crossing or something.
And the sun's out, you know.
Hey! Yes, we walked a lot.
Hey!
All right, all right.
I'm here to cut the ocean.
Let's do it right here.
Let's do it. Hey, let's do it.
Keep filming, please.
Oh, yeah!
Rainbow, rainbow, rainbow. Isn't that a rainbow?
Oh, my God!
Wow!
That's great!
We managed to capture a rainbow at the very end!
Oh, thank God!
I got a great shot.
Hey, I was right inside the rainbow!
Yeah, it was amazing!
It was so beautiful today.
Oh, I felt so much love.
I'm so glad.
Thank you so much.
It's going to last forever.
That's how the shoot ended.
I'm thinking of making an album of the photos I just took.
I'd like to leave it as an album or something, so please wait a minute.
So please wait a bit.
Oh, no!
I'm so happy, I can't wait to give it to you!
Anyway, until I give it to you...
Yes, I'll look forward to it a little bit. Yes, I'll look forward to it a bit.
Wait and see.
So, it's finally done, and I'd like to go give you the finished product.
Hello.
Yes, ma'am.
My name is Miigurin.
I have some free time today,
I have something to give you.
Of course.
Excuse me.
Finally,
Yes.
It's done.
Wow!
Thank you very much.
Now, I will award it to you.
Here you go.
Thank you very much.
Wait, that's so neat.
I can see that now.
May I open this?
Sure.
I'll open it.
It's your Christmas present today. It's a Christmas present, today.
It's Christmas.
It's Christmas Eve.
I'm glad, I'm glad, I'm glad.
Se-no, se-no, you.
No way.
Oh, no way.
This is amazing.
What, a photo book?
Ehhhh.
It's in an effect case.
That's amazing.
Wait a minute.
I'm sorry. I'm just too excited.
Oh, wait.
It arrived.
It's a photo book.
May I take a look inside?
Yes.
What? Wait a minute.
What? You can make this. You can make something like this?
I'll open it.
I'm sorry. I didn't expect it to come out like a book.
I mean, you were on a pretty tight schedule.
I was too surprised. I was so surprised.
I'm off.
Eh...
Oh, no.
Wow.
It's beautiful. I'm embarrassed to say it myself.
No, it's nice.
It's good.
It's nice.
Oh, the front.
You can see the furisode well.
It's my mother's furisode.
Wow.
It's nice.
I'm embarrassed to say it's nice.
It's the only one of its kind in the world, so I really only made one.
Wow. I'm so happy.
I'm thinking of making one myself.
It's so nice.
And something.
Ah, there it is.
Ta-da.
I did my best.
It's a rainbow series.
Amazing.
I knew it. This is the best rainbow I've ever seen. I knew it, and I'm glad this is the best rainbow I've seen this time around.
It's good. Here.
Cahn.
Oh, to the back.
Even the back.
Even the backside stars are in place.
I'm glad.
I thought of a hair out.
Amazing.
It looks like this.
It's too amazing.
Yay.
Wow. Thank you very much.
What do you think?
I had no idea that you could make such a wonderful album.
I had a lot of fun shooting it,
During the live rehearsal, I was told not to watch you working on the computer,
I felt really bad about that,
But I am so happy to have received such a wonderful piece of work,
I'm glad I asked Mikumi to do it.
Thank you very much. Thank you very much.
Thank you for this commemorative book.
It was the first time for me to show it like this, so I was nervous,
But I'm glad. I'm glad you liked it.
It's wonderful. It's the only one of its kind in the world,
I'm sorry.Excuse me.
I want my family to see this.
It's probably worth a lot of money,
I won't give it to everyone.
I don't have it.
I'm the only one who has it.
Thank you very much. Really.
Let's go take pictures again. Someday.
Someday. Someday in plain clothes.
Yes, that's right.
I look forward to working with you.
Congratulations, Seijin.
Thank you very much.
Lovely.
Good button and if you like this content,
Subscribe to our channel.
See you soon.
Please subscribe to our channel.